I sell plastic surgery business consulting.
We're doing 1.2 million right now.
I'd like to get to 5 million in the next three years.
Every problem that we find, I want to fix for them,
so we now do hiring for them.
We'll do their HR, we're kind of all over the place.
Is there something that you do that's very valuable
that takes you less time, that's more repeatable
than other things that you do?
Honestly, that's probably the HR and hiring side,
which is the least exciting, but.
Well, boring businesses make lots of money,
so I'm a big fan of that.
What would stop you from just doing that
as the primary thing you do?
I guess it just sounds boring to me.
That's not as exciting.
What's really valuable, at least for me,
is understanding that it is not my business's job
to satisfy my intellectual curiosity.
My business's job is to serve my customers,
not my personal needs, my emotional needs.
A lot of it is like, repeat successful actions,
do the boring work.
The reason I say those things is because
that is kind of what it sounds like.